Hello everyone and welcome to EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎收听EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
My name is Catherine and today we're going to be helping you set up an answering machine
我是Catherine，今天我们要帮你设置一个答录机。
basically.
基本上是这样。
That's right.
没错。
So somebody's calling you, you can't answer the phone so you leave a message and we're
所以有人打电话给你，你没法接电话，就留个言，我们今天要教你这些。
going to teach you all about that today.
没错。
That's right.
So let's take a listen to our dialogue and we'll be back in a moment to figure out just
那我们先听一段对话，一会儿回来再分析。
what's going on.
到底是怎么回事。
Can you help me set up my voicemail message?
你能帮我设置语音信箱留言吗？
I just got this service and I'm not really sure what I'm supposed to say.
我刚开通这个服务，不太确定该说什么。
Sure.
当然可以。
You just basically got to let the caller know who they called and ask them for their contact
你基本上只需要让来电者知道他们打给了谁，然后请他们留下联系方式。
information so you can call them back.
这样你就能回电话给他们。
Okay.
好的。
So I can say, this is Abby's voicemail.
所以我可以这样说：这是Abby的语音信箱。
I will call you later.
我稍后会给你回电话。
So leave me your name and number.
所以请留下你的名字和号码。
That's more or less the idea, but try something that sounds more friendly.
差不多是这个意思，但试试听起来更友好一些的。
Okay.
好的。
So how about this?
那这样怎么样？
This is Abby and I'm really happy you called.
我是Abby，很高兴你打来电话。
I promise I will give you a ring as soon as I can.
我保证会尽快给你回电。
So please leave me your name and number.
所以请留下你的名字和号码。
Talk to you soon.
回头聊。
A little too friendly, Abby.
有点太友好了，Abby。
Just say this.
就这样说吧。
Hi, you've reached Abby.
嗨，你已接通Abby的语音信箱。
I'm unable to answer your call right now, but if you leave me your name and phone number,
我现在无法接听你的电话，但如果你留下名字和电话号码。
I will get back to you as soon as possible.
我会尽快回复你。
Thanks.
谢谢。
That's perfect.
完美。
Can you say that again and record it for me?
你能再说一遍并帮我录下来吗？
All right, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So now let's take a look at some language takeaway.
现在来看看一些语言要点。
Language takeaway.
语言要点。
All right.
好的。
In the first sentence, we are asking someone to help me set up my voicemail message.
在第一句话中，我们请别人帮我设置语音信箱留言。
So we got two key words there.
所以这里有两个关键词。
That's right.
没错。
So let's break it up.
那我们分解一下。
The first one is a phrasal verb, to set up.
第一个是短语动词，to set up。
Okay.
好的。
You can set a lot of things up, but just remember that set and up, these are the two words that
你可以设置很多东西，但记住set和up是连在一起的。
go together.
这两个词。
In this case, we're setting up voicemail.
在这个例子中，我们在设置语音信箱。
It means to establish or to start or to put together.
意思是建立、开始或组装。
Yeah, to install.
对，安装。
Like for example, you get a new computer and you have to connect all the cables and you
比如，你买了台新电脑，需要连接所有线缆。
have to connect the monitor.
还要连接显示器。
So you say, can you help me set up my computer?
所以你说：你能帮我设置电脑吗？
That's right.
没错。
So he always helps me set it up.
所以他总是帮我设置它。
So my computer, for example.
比如我的电脑。
That's right.
没错。
And what we're setting up is our voicemail message.
而我们要设置的是语音信箱留言。
So what exactly is voicemail?
那语音信箱到底是什么？
Well you know what mail is.
嗯，你知道邮件是什么。
We have email and regular mail.
我们有电子邮件和普通邮件。
Voicemail is the kind of message you receive on your phone, your cell phone or your home
语音信箱是你手机上收到的一种消息，手机或座机。
phone when you don't answer the phone.
当你不接电话时。
That's right.
没错。
So basically a way for people to leave you a message even though you can't answer them.
所以基本上是一种让别人给你留言的方式，即使你无法接听。
That's right.
没错。
So this is something that's, it's not text, it's actually a voice.
所以这不是文字，而是声音。
So that's why it's called voicemail and you have to set it up.
所以叫语音信箱，你需要设置它。
Okay.
好的。
So there's, there's no automatic voicemail message.
所以没有自动的语音信箱留言。
You actually have to make your own or you can choose one.
你实际上得自己做，或者选一个。
And today we're making our own.
今天我们自己做。
That's right.
没错。
And so we're explaining that we actually just got this service and we don't really know
所以我们解释我们刚开通这个服务，不太清楚。
what we're supposed to say or how to set up our voicemail.
该说什么或怎么设置语音信箱。
That's right.
没错。
So voicemail messages are a kind of service.
所以语音信箱留言是一种服务。
And now who would offer this kind of service, Marco?
那谁会提供这种服务呢，Marco？
Probably your telephone company.
可能是你的电话公司。
That's right.
没错。
So a telephone company will offer many different services and these are things that you can
所以电话公司会提供很多不同的服务，这些都是你可以用的。
pay extra for and they're useful.
需要额外付费，而且它们很有用。
They can help you in some way.
它们能在某些方面帮助你。
So another kind of service is three-way calling.
所以另一种服务是三方通话。
Right.
对。
That's right.
没错。
So actually we're taking a look at this word service as a noun.
实际上我们正在看“service”这个词作为名词的用法。
So we have a service or this service.
所以我们有“a service”或“this service”。
So the company offers this service.
所以公司提供这项服务。
And well, why are we setting up the voicemail?
那么，我们为什么要设置语音信箱呢？
And our friend explains that we just basically doing it to let the caller know who they called.
我们的朋友解释说，我们这样做基本上是为了让来电者知道他们打给了谁。
Okay.
好的。
So if I call a number and it says, Hey, leave a message.
所以如果我打一个号码，它说“嘿，留言吧”。
I don't know who I'm leaving a message for.
我不知道我在给谁留言。
Did I dial the wrong number?
我是不是拨错号码了？
What do I say?
我该说什么？
Do I say my phone number?
我该说我的电话号码吗？
So this is basically instructions for what to say.
所以这基本上是关于该说什么的指导。
That's right.
没错。
And you become the caller.
而你变成了来电者。
Right.
对。
So whoever is making the call is called the caller.
所以任何打电话的人都被称为“caller”（来电者）。
And this is why we are setting up our voicemail to let the caller know who we are calling.
这就是为什么我们要设置语音信箱，让来电者知道他们打给了谁。
And of course we have to ask the caller for their contact information.
当然，我们还得请来电者留下他们的联系方式。
All right.
好的。
Now this is important because it's not just something you have with voicemail messages.
这很重要，因为它不仅仅适用于语音信箱留言。
You have contact information for many different things.
你在很多不同的事情上都需要联系方式。
For example, your medical care, your school, you have to include contact information.
比如，你的医疗保健、你的学校，你都必须包含联系方式。
Now this would be your phone number, your address and or your email.
这包括你的电话号码、地址和/或电子邮件。
That's right.
没错。
So your contact information is not only useful for in a voicemail message, but for example,
所以你的联系方式不仅在语音信箱留言中有用，例如，
in a business meeting or a business lunch, you want to get maybe someone else's contact
在商务会议或商务午餐中，你可能想拿到别人的联系
information so you can call them later.
信息，以便以后给他们打电话。
That's right.
没错。
So don't forget, it's also your name as well.
所以别忘了，也包括你的名字。
So I forgot to mention that.
我忘了提这一点。
That's right.
没错。
Contact information must have your name.
联系方式必须包含你的名字。
All right.
好的。
So that's pretty much all we have for the first part of language takeaway.
这就是语言要点第一部分的全部内容。
Why don't we listen to the dialogue again and we'll be back in a bit with Fluency Builder.
我们不如再听一遍对话，稍后回来继续“流利度训练”。
Can you help me set up my voicemail message?
你能帮我设置我的语音信箱留言吗？
I just got the service and I'm not really sure what I'm supposed to say.
我刚开通这项服务，不太确定该说什么。
Sure.
当然。
You just basically got to let the caller know who they called and ask them for their contact
你基本上只需要让来电者知道他们打给了谁，并请他们留下联系
information so you can call them back.
信息，这样你就可以回电。
Okay.
好的。
So I can say, this is Abby's voicemail.
所以我可以这样说：“这是艾比的语音信箱。”
I will call you later.
“我会稍后给你回电。”
So leave me your name and number.
“所以请留下你的名字和号码。”
That's more or less the idea, but try something that sounds more friendly.
大致是这个意思，但试试听起来更友好一些的。
Okay.
好的。
So how about this?
那这个怎么样？
This is Abby and I'm really happy you called.
“我是艾比，很高兴你打来电话。”
I promise I will give you a ring as soon as I can.
“我保证会尽快给你回电。”
So please leave me your name and number.
“所以请留下你的名字和号码。”
Talk to you soon.
“回头聊。”
A little too friendly, Abby.
有点太友好了，艾比。
Just say this.
就这样说：
Hi, you've reached Abby.
“嗨，你已接通艾比的语音信箱。”
I'm unable to answer your call right now, but if you leave me your name and phone number,
“我现在无法接听你的电话，但如果你留下你的名字和电话号码，
I will get back to you as soon as possible.
我会尽快回复你。”
Thanks.
“谢谢。”
That's perfect.
这很完美。
Can you say that again and record it for me?
你能再说一遍并帮我录下来吗？
All right, here we are in Fluency Builder and the first phrase we've got is, how about
好的，现在我们进入“流利度训练”，第一个短语是“how about
this?
this？”（这个怎么样？）
So we're saying, we've got an example for you.
所以我们在说，我们给你一个例子。
How about this?
这个怎么样？
That's right.
没错。
Then the example.
然后是例子。
So we've talked about how about many times already.
我们已经多次讨论过“how about”的用法。
So for example, how about we go to the movies or how not to say how about your weekend because
比如，“how about we go to the movies”（我们去看电影怎么样）或者不要说“how about your weekend”（你的周末怎么样），因为
that's completely wrong.
那完全是错的。
In this occasion, we're talking about how about this and this is like setting it up
在这个场合，我们在说“how about this”，这就像是为
for an example.
一个例子做铺垫。
That's right.
没错。
So for another example, we could say, so Marco, I'm trying to figure out how to say hello
所以再举个例子，我们可以说，马可，我在想怎么在接电话时说“你好”，
when I answer the phone because I don't like the way I say it now.
因为我不喜欢我现在的说法。
I can say, how about this?
我可以说：“这个怎么样？”
Hello?
“你好？”
Is that good?
那好吗？
No?
不好吗？
That's all right.
没关系。
That's right.
没错。
Hello.
你好。
That's too strong.
那太强烈了。
Yeah, that's good.
是的，那很好。
All right.
好的。
So basically I'm setting up an example.
所以基本上我在举一个例子。
I'm saying, okay, keep listening.
我在说，好的，继续听。
I will give you an example.
我会给你一个例子。
Yeah.
是的。
Just imagine that you're trying on different clothes and someone is giving you their opinion.
想象一下你在试穿不同的衣服，有人给你意见。
So maybe you try on a black shirt and you say, how about this one?
也许你试了一件黑衬衫，然后你说，这件怎么样？
Eh, boring.
嗯，无聊。
And then you try on a green one and you say, now how about this?
然后你试了一件绿色的，你说，现在这件怎么样？
Better.
更好。
Right.
对。
So then you're giving them other options and examples and this is why we say, how about
所以你给他们其他选择和例子，这就是为什么我们说，这个
this?
怎么样？
And then we give the example like Abby did.
然后我们像Abby那样举例子。
And you're also asking for a response.
而且你也在寻求回应。
You're asking for an opinion.
你在征求意见。
And so what Abby's saying is, I promise I will give you a ring as soon as I can.
所以Abby说的是，我保证我会尽快给你打电话。
Now this phrase, give you a ring is very British English, but it's also something you should
这个短语“give you a ring”是非常英式的英语，但如果你想在美国生活，你也应该
know if you want to be in America because you'll hear it in TV and stuff.
知道，因为你会从电视等地方听到它。
That's right.
没错。
It's actually a colloquial term for saying, I will call you.
这实际上是一个口语说法，意思是“我会打电话给你”。
I will call you.
我会打电话给你。
I will call you back or I will give you a call.
我会回电话给你，或者我会给你打个电话。
So the telephone rings.
所以电话铃响了。
That's the verb that goes with the phone, right?
那是和电话搭配的动词，对吧？
Ring ring.
叮铃叮铃。
So I will give you a ring means I will call you just like you just said, Marco.
所以“I will give you a ring”意思就是我会打电话给你，就像你刚才说的，Marco。
That's right.
没错。
So remember this phrase.
所以记住这个短语。
It's actually, it may seem a little bit confusing, but remember it has to do with calling someone.
它可能看起来有点让人困惑，但记住它和打电话有关。
I will give you a ring is I will call you.
“I will give you a ring”就是我会打电话给你。
Or if you say, hey, give me a ring later on this afternoon.
或者如果你说，嘿，今天下午晚些时候给我打个电话。
It's call me later this afternoon.
就是今天下午晚些时候打给我。
All right.
好的。
And then moving towards the end of the dialogue, Abby says, hi, you have reached Abby.
然后到对话的结尾，Abby说，嗨，你已接通Abby。
Okay.
好的。
This is weird because she is Abby, but she's saying you have reached Abby, right?
这有点奇怪，因为她是Abby，但她说“你已接通Abby”，对吧？
You're speaking about yourself in the third person.
你在用第三人称谈论自己。
That's right.
没错。
So this is a message.
所以这是一条留言。
So you're telling people what to do.
所以你在告诉别人该做什么。
Like I said, they're instructions.
就像我说的，这是指示。
And so this is basically the first thing you say, you have reached Catherine.
所以这基本上是你说的第一句话，你已接通Catherine。
That means the number you dialed is Catherine's phone number, right?
这意味着你拨打的号码是Catherine的电话号码，对吧？
So you reached, that means that you've contacted.
所以“你已接通”意思是你已经联系上了。
Right.
对。
Exactly.
完全正确。
So as you said, it's important if you ever call a bank or in, or any type of company,
所以就像你说的，如果你打电话给银行或任何类型的公司，这很重要，
it will say you have reached a Wells Fargo bank or something, and it'll give you, it'll
它会说“你已接通富国银行”之类的，然后它会告诉你
tell you what number you called because maybe you put in your finger wrong and you just
你拨打的号码，因为也许你按错了手指，刚刚
called the wrong number.
拨错了号码。
That's right.
没错。
Or you could use the word reached in a different way.
或者你可以用不同的方式使用“reached”这个词。
For example, yesterday I was very angry at Marco because I couldn't reach him by phone.
例如，昨天我对Marco很生气，因为我打电话联系不上他。
I called and called and called and couldn't reach him.
我打了一遍又一遍，就是联系不上他。
And I realized then his phone is broken.
然后我才意识到他的手机坏了。
That's right.
没错。
So actually this verb to reach someone also has to do with, with, in general with calling.
所以实际上这个动词“to reach someone”通常也和打电话有关。
I was trying to reach you all afternoon, but I couldn't get a hold of you.
我整个下午都在试着联系你，但就是找不到你。
That's right.
没错。
And I was so frustrated.
我当时非常沮丧。
Well, actually, if I had voicemail, I would continue by saying, I am unable to answer
嗯，实际上，如果我有语音信箱，我会接着说，我现在无法接听
your call right now because maybe my phone is off.
你的电话，因为也许我的手机关机了。
Maybe I am busy.
也许我很忙。
So we say, I am unable to answer your call right now.
所以我们说，我现在无法接听你的电话。
All right.
好的。
Now this seems really long.
现在这看起来很长。
Okay.
好的。
It's a little bit strange, but this is basically the standard for how to record a message.
这有点奇怪，但这基本上是录制留言的标准方式。
I'm unable to answer your call right now.
我现在无法接听你的电话。
So you answer the phone, right?
所以你接电话，对吧？
Or you answer a phone call.
或者你接听一个电话。
But in this case, I'm unable to, that means I can't talk to you for whatever reason.
但在这种情况下，“我无法”意思是出于某种原因我不能和你说话。
I'm out of the house.
我不在家。
I'm busy.
我很忙。
So I'm unable to answer your call right now.
所以我暂时无法接听你的电话。
Just remember that that means I can't talk to you right now.
请记住，这意味着我现在不能和你通话。
I can't be on the phone.
我不能接电话。
And actually this word unable sounds a lot more polite and a lot more formal than saying
实际上，“unable”这个词听起来比说“I can't”要礼貌和正式得多。
I can't.
我不能。
That's right.
没错。
And that's why we use it on messages like this because it is so polite and so nice.
这就是为什么我们在这样的留言中使用它，因为它非常礼貌和得体。
That's right.
没错。
All right.
好了。
So that's all the time we have for Fluency Builder.
这就是我们“流利度训练”的全部内容。
Let's take a listen to our dialogue one last time.
让我们最后听一遍对话。
Can you help me set up my voicemail message?
你能帮我设置语音信箱留言吗？
I just got this service.
我刚开通这项服务。
And I'm not really sure what I'm supposed to say.
我不太确定该说什么。
Sure.
当然可以。
You just basically got to let the caller know who they called and ask them for their contact
你基本上只需要让来电者知道他们打给了谁，并请他们留下联系方式，
information so you can call them back.
这样你就可以回电给他们。
Okay.
好的。
So I can say, this is Abby's voicemail.
所以我可以这样说：这是艾比的语音信箱。
I will call you later.
我稍后会给你回电话。
So leave me your name and number.
所以请留下你的名字和电话号码。
That's more or less the idea.
大致就是这个意思。
But try something that sounds more friendly.
但试试听起来更友好一些的说法。
Okay.
好的。
So how about this?
那这样怎么样？
This is Abby and I'm really happy you called.
这是艾比，很高兴你打来电话。
I promise I will give you a ring as soon as I can.
我保证会尽快给你回电。
So please leave me your name and number.
所以请留下你的名字和电话号码。
Talk to you soon.
回头聊。
A little too friendly, Abby.
有点太友好了，艾比。
Just say this.
就这样说吧。
Hi, you've reached Abby.
嗨，你已接通艾比的电话。
I'm unable to answer your call right now.
我现在无法接听你的电话。
But if you leave me your name and phone number, I will get back to you as soon as possible.
但如果你留下名字和电话号码，我会尽快回复你。
Thanks.
谢谢。
That's perfect.
这太完美了。
Can you say that again and record it for me?
你能再说一遍并帮我录下来吗？
All right.
好的。
So talking about voicemail, I think in the United States, this is a very, very popular
说到语音信箱，我觉得在美国，这是一种非常非常普遍
and almost necessary service.
而且几乎是必需的服务。
That's right.
没错。
So in America, if you buy a phone plan, which most people have, that means that you can
所以在美国，如果你买了一个手机套餐——大多数人都有——那就意味着你可以
use your phone in a certain way.
以某种方式使用你的手机。
Like every day you have free nights or you have a thousand minutes per month to talk.
比如每天有免费夜间通话，或者每月有一千分钟的通话时间。
But you sometimes also get these services or you pay extra for them.
但有时你也会获得这些服务，或者需要额外付费。
And voicemail is very important because people don't text as much in America as they do in
而语音信箱非常重要，因为在美国，人们不像其他国家那样频繁发短信。
other countries.
其他国家。
So I know in other places, sometimes you text a message to someone and they receive it and
所以我知道在其他地方，有时你给别人发一条短信，他们收到后，
okay, it's a message.
好吧，这就是一条消息。
But if you don't do that, you actually have to record a message.
但如果你不那样做，你就得录一段留言。
Like when I call my parents, they never answer the phone.
比如我给我父母打电话时，他们从来不接。
So I always have to leave a voicemail message.
所以我总是得留个语音留言。
So I say, hi, it's Catherine.
于是我就说：嗨，我是凯瑟琳。
It's Saturday.
今天是星期六。
Where are you?
你在哪儿？
Call me.
给我回电话。
Right.
对。
Okay.
好的。
So that's that kind of, I think, cultural behavior that we just expect to leave messages
所以我觉得，这大概是一种文化行为，我们就是习惯给美国人留言。
for people in America.
在美国就是这样。
And it's actually interesting because I've been to other countries where they also have
其实挺有意思的，因为我去过其他国家，那里也有语音信箱和这项服务。
voicemail messages and the service, but people are not as willing to actually leave the message.
但人们不太愿意真的留言。
So it happened to me.
我就遇到过这种情况。
For example, I call someone, I get their voicemail and I don't leave a message.
比如，我打电话给别人，听到语音信箱，我就不留言。
I just hang up.
直接挂断。
And then they have...
然后他们就有...
You're bored or you're uncomfortable?
你是觉得无聊还是不舒服？
Why?
为什么？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Because, you know, if you have a mobile phone, it'll show up anyways that you have a missed
因为，你知道，如果你有手机，它总会显示你有一个未接来电。
call from this person.
来自这个人。
So then I really just, I don't really leave the message anymore.
所以我现在真的，基本上不留言了。
It's like, okay, you saw that I called you.
就像，好吧，你看到我打过电话了。
Either I'll just call you back later or you'll call me back when you see the missed call.
要么我晚点再打给你，要么你看到未接来电后回我电话。
But yeah, for homes, obviously it's different.
但说到家里座机，显然就不一样了。
You need to leave a message if you call someone.
你打电话给别人，就得留言。
Although sometimes it can be a bad thing.
虽然有时候这也不是好事。
I definitely have a friend who loves to leave long messages.
我确实有个朋友特别喜欢留长留言。
Oh, really?
哦，真的吗？
Hey, Catherine, it's me.
嘿，凯瑟琳，是我。
So it's like Saturday at four o'clock and I was just thinking about calling and I was
所以现在是周六下午四点，我刚才想着打电话，然后我
going to come over but I decided not to come over.
打算过来，但决定不来了。
But then I was thinking maybe I'll just call you instead and I can see that you're not
但后来我又想，不如就打电话给你吧，我看你不在
home, but maybe you're out to dinner.
家，但也许你出去吃饭了。
I remember you saying...
我记得你说过……
And they just go on and on and on.
他们就这样没完没了地说下去。
You actually, there is an end.
其实，是有结束的。
They'll go beep and then it cuts you off.
他们会“哔”一声，然后挂断。
Right.
对。
I think it's like 30 seconds or something like this.
我觉得大概有30秒左右。
So it's very interesting, this whole voicemail thing, especially in the business world as
所以整个语音信箱这事儿挺有意思的，尤其是在商业领域
well.
也是。
Many times people go into a meeting, turn off their phones or put it on silent.
很多时候人们去开会，会关掉手机或调成静音。
And if you want to reach them or you want to leave a message, you've got to do the voicemail.
如果你想联系他们或留言，就得用语音信箱。
Yeah, calls will go right to voicemail so that you don't interrupt the meeting.
是啊，电话会直接转到语音信箱，这样就不会打扰会议。
Exactly.
没错。
So that's all the time we have for today.
那我们今天的时间就到这里。
Come to EnglishPod.com.
来EnglishPod.com吧。
We more than welcome your questions, your comments, any suggestions.
我们非常欢迎你的问题、评论和任何建议。
You can find us there, EnglishPod.com.
你可以在那里找到我们，EnglishPod.com。
See you.
再见。
Bye-bye.
拜拜。
Have a great day.
祝你有美好的一天。